Guide to the Samuel R. Delany Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- May 2017 acquisition, 200.17; (249 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  - Materials deposited in 2003, 1969-2003; 7.42; (7 boxes)
    - Printed material, 1999-2003-05
      - Bound proofs, undated
        - "Aye and Gomorrah", undated (Box 98)
      - Newspapers, 2003-04-27-2003-05
        - 'New York Times Book Review', 2003-04-27 (Box 100)
        - 'Aurthur', 2003-05 (Box 100)
        - 'LA Weekly', Vol. 25, No. 25, 2003-05-09-2003-05-15 (Box 100)
      - Miscellaneous printed material, 1999-2002 (Box 98)
        Contains: miscellaneous printed material. Includes: PMLA program (2002 November); 3 Readercon souvenir books (1999, 2001, 2002).
      - Miscellaneous printed material, undated; (2 folders) (Box 99)
        Contains: miscellaneous printed material. Includes: pamphlets, flyers, booklets, printed mailings. Also includes: photocopied material from printed books.
    - Professional material, undated
      - Notes, undated (Box 99)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box 99)
      - Minutes, undated (Box 99)
    - Miscellanous, undated
      - Miscellaneous materials, including pharmacy receipts, name tags, 1 photograph, undated (Box 99)
        Includes: pharmacy receipts; name tags; 1 photoprint of SRD.
    - Oversize material, 1987-2003-06-11
      - Laminated newspaper articles, 2002-04-21-2003-06-11
        - 'Chicago Tribune Tempo', 2003-06-11 (Box 174 (Oversize))
        - 'LA Weekly', 2003-05-09-2003-05-15 (Box 174 (Oversize))
        - 'New York Times Book Review', 2003-04-27 (Box 174 (Oversize))
        - 'New York Times Book Review', 2002-04-21 (Box 174 (Oversize))
        - 'Brooklyn Free Press', 2002-11-29-2002-12-05 (Box 174 (Oversize))
      - Laminated flyer for "The Tale of Plagues and Carnivals", 1987 (Box 174 (Oversize))
        Contains: laminated flyer for "The Tale of Plagues and Carnivals", 2 copies.
  - Materials deposited in 2004, 1942-1987-11; 6.83; (9 boxes)
    - Printed material, 1959-1987-11
      - Booklets, undated
        - "The American Theatre for Poets", undated (Box 101)
        - "Jargon 31:14 Poets, 1 Artist", undated (Box 101)
        - "In God We Trust", undated (Box 101)
        - "Supplement To Now", signed by Basil King, undated (Box 101)
        - "Foot", signed by poet Joanne Elizabeth Kyger, undated (Box 101)
        - "Sore Finger", undated (Box 101)
        - "Kodak Gray Scale", undated (Box 101)
        - "Toward a Female Liberation Movement", undated (Box 101)
        - "American Women: Their Use and Abuse", undated (Box 101)
        - "The Holy Grail", undated (Box 101)
        - "My Father's Golden Eye", signed by author Tom Veitch, undated (Box 101)
        - "Quark III", undated (Box 101)
        - Untitled, signed by John [illegible], undated (Box 101)
        - "Does the Secret mind Whisper" by Bob Kaufman, undated (Box 101)
      - Comic books, undated
        - "Zap Comix" No. 1-2, 5, undated (Box 101)
          Also includes: "All New Underground Comix Armageddon #1"; "The Adventures of the Little Green Dinosaur"; "Mr. Natural"; "It's That Fresh Kid from Cleveland Eggs Ackley"; "Brain Fantasy"; "Black Magic"; "Mother Oats".
        - "Masterpiece on the Shithouse Wall", undated (Box 101)
          Also includes: "Laugh in the Dark"; "Slow Death"; "Big Ass Comics No. 2"; "San Francisco Comic Book"; "Feds 'N' Heads Comics"; "The Collected Adventures of the Faburlous Furry Freak Brothers"; "Further Adventures of Those Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers"; "Tales of Sex and Death".
      - Ten newspaper clippings, 1965-08-1987-11 (Box 102)
      - "Boghosian", booklet / catalog, undated (Box 102)
        Contains: "Boghosian", booklet/catalog.
      - Programs (Box 102)
        Contains: 4 programs. Includes programs for: Children's Book Festival; Bimbo's Theatre Restaurant; Saint Lousicon Pocket Porgram; Les Bonnes (The Maids) par Jean Genet.
      - Proofs, undated
        - "Doctor Mirabilis" by James Blish, undated (Box 102)
        - 'Nova' by SRD, undated (Box 102)
          Contains: proof of 'Nova', novel by SRD.
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 102)
          Contains: miscellaneous proofs. Also includes: portion of 'Nova' proof from previous file.
      - Magazines, 1968-1974
        - 'Just Friends', Issues 1-2, undated, 1969 - 1971 (Box 102)
          Contains: 'Just Friends', issues 1-2, some duplicates (undated). Also includes: 'Cow', two issues (undated); 'SFWA Forum', seven issues (1969-1971).
        - 'ARX', 1969-1970 (Box 102)
          Contains: 'ARX', six issues (?) (1969-1970). ALso includes: 'Caterpillar II' (1970 spring).
        - 'Aphra', Vol. 2, No. 1 and 4, 1970 winter - 1971 fall (Box 102)
          Contains: 'Aphra', Vol. 2, No. 1 and 4, some duplicates (1970 winter - 1971 fall). Also includes: 'The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction', three issues (1968 May - 1971 July).
        - 'Science Fiction Analog', 1969-1974 (Box 102)
          Contains: 'Science Fiction Analaog', two issues (1969 September - 1974 October). Also includes: untitled poetry (undated); 'Hyper Drive', Vol. 1, No. 2 (undated); 'Speculation', Vol. 3, No. 1 (1970 January); 'Kinesis', Issue 1 (1969 February).
        - 'Toothpaste' 5, undated (Box 102)
          Contains: 'Toothpaste' 5. Also includes: 'BeABohema' 7; 'New Worlds', No. 192.
        - 'May' 4, 1969, undated (Box 102)
          Contains: 'May' 4 (1969). Also includes: 'Vector' (1969 January); 'Odd', No. 22 (1969 summer); 'The Family Store', Spring no. 2 (undated).
        - 'Magazine' 2-4, undated (Box 103)
          Contains: 'Magazine' 2-4, some duplicates.
      - Newsletters and bulletins, 1969-1980
        - 'Extrapolation', 1969-1970 (Box 103)
          Contains: 'Extrapolation', Vol. X, no. 2 (1969 May), Vol. 11, no. 2 (1970 May). Also includes: 'SFWA Bulletin', Vol. 5, No. 1 (1969 February), Vol. 7, No. 5 (1970 April); 'SFWA Newsletters', No. 3 (1969).
        - 'Urania', 1969 - 1980, undated (Box 104)
          Contains: 'Urania' (1980). Also includes: 'Ms. On the Arts' (undated); 'Sci-Fi Collections' (undated); 'The Daily Planet' (1969); 'The Dancing Gryphon' (1969); 'The Fried Hat Review', no. 4 (1969); 'The 10th Muse' (undated); 'Cat 22' (undated).
        - Miscellaneous, undated; (2 folders) (Box 103)
          Contains: miscellaneous newsletters and bulletins.
      - Journals, 1959-1971
        - 'Open Places', Issues 1-8, 1966-11-1970-06 (Box 103)
          Contains: 'Open Places', Issues 1-8, some duplicates (1966 November - 1970 March). Also includes: 'Poetry Norwest' (1969 March - 1970 June).
        - 'Riverside Quarterly', 1963-1970 (Box 103)
          Contains: 'Riverside Quarterly' (1969 March - 1970 June). Also includes: 'Yugen' 7 (undated); 'Genesis West' (1963 spring); 'Poet Lore' (1968 fall); 'Epoch' (1969 spring); 'New York Quarterly' (1970 winter).
        - 'Gum', 1959-1971 (Box 103)
          Contains: 'Gum' (1971). Also includes: 'Pacific Nation', 1 duplicate (1969 February); 'Man-Root', Issues 1-2, 1 duplicate (1969 August - 1970 January); reviews (including: 'Northwest Review', 'Evergreen Review', 'The Galley Sail Review', 'Columbia Review') (circa 1959 - 1969).
        - Reviews, 1968-08-1971-12 (Box 103)
          Contains: 'Six Science Fiction Review' (1969 June - 1970 August); 'Evergreen' (1971 December); 'The Wivenhoe Park Review' (1968 August).
        - 'Ephemeris' 1-2, undated, 1969 March (Box 103)
          Contains: 'Ephemeris' 1-2 (undated). Also includes: 'Kinesis' 2 (1969 March).
        - 'Adventures in Poetry', 1969 January - 1971 summer (Box 103)
          Contains: 'Adventures in Poetry', five issues.
        - 'Oriental Blue Streak', 1968 - 1971, undated (Box 103)
          Contains: 'Oriental Blue Streak' (1968 spring). Also includes: 'Adventures in Poetry', portion of five issues from previous file (1969 January - 1971 summer); 'Determination Our Motto' (undated); 'Nozdrovia' (1968).
    - Notebooks, undated
      - Four spiral bound notebooks, undated; (4 folders) (Box 104)
        Contains: 4 holograph spiral bound notebooks, including one re: "Landscapes and Contrivance for 'The Book'".
      - Two bound notebooks, undated; (2 folders) (Box 104)
        Contains: two holograph notebooks, bound.
    - Printed material (continued), 1961-1971
      - Journals (continued), 1961-1971
        - 'Ephemeris III', 1961-1971 (Box 105)
          Contains: 'Ephemeris III' (1969 December). Also includes: 'The San Francisco Quarterly' (1970 winter); 'Journal for the Protection of All Being' (1961); 'The World' (1971); 'The Word Is Freed' (1969 July); 'The Rivoli Review' (1964); 'Telephone' (undated); 'City', three issues (1967 - 1968); 'City' 5, three copies, includes one black and white print of cover (undated).
    - Financial material, 1968-1970
      - Checks, 1969-1970 (Box 105)
        Contains: approximately 140 returned checks; 3 check registers.
      - Financial statements and receipts, 1968-1970 (Box 106)
        Contains: 11 royalty statements (1968-1969); 38 receipts (1969-1970); 6 tax return statements (1968-1969); 1 investment statement (1968 December); 18 bank statements re: Liberty National Bank (1969-1970); 3 miscellaneous bank items (undated).
    - Medical records, undated
      - Booklets relating to health insurance, undated (Box 106)
        Contains: four booklets relating to health insurance.
      - Appointment card, undated (Box 106)
        Contains: one appointment card.
      - Medical bills, undated (Box 106)
        Contains: two medical bills.
      - Blood sugar chart, undated (Box 106)
    - Legal material, 1942
      - Birth certificate, 1942 (Box 106)
      - Contract, undated (Box 106)
      - Charge card, undated (Box 106)
      - Social Security card, undated (Box 106)
    - Personal memorabilia, 1969
      - Tickets, 1969 (Box 106)
        Contains: six tickets, including plane and train tickets.
    - Professional material, undated
      - Resumes, undated (Box 106)
        Contains: three resumes.
      - Statement of payment for film review, undated (Box 106)
      - Agreement contract between Paperback Library and SRD for WARP, undated (Box 106)
      - Business cards, undated (Box 106)
        Contains: three business cards.
      - Student records re: Hilda Hacker, undated (Box 106)
    - Artwork, undated
      - Drawings, undated (Box 106)
        Contains: fourteen drawings.
      - Astrological charts, undated (Box 106)
        Contains: three astrological charts.
      - Watercolor portrait, undated (Box 106)
      - Flyer for the "Committee for Homosexual Freedom", undated (Box 106)
      - Portfolio by Don Simpson, undated (Box 106)
        Contains: portfolio by Don Simpson. Includes: thirteen black and white photoprints.
    - Photographs, undated
      - Prints, undated
        - Nine black and white photos, undated (Box 105)
        - Five color photos, undated (Box 105)
    - Correspondence, 1968-01-09-1977-12-23
      - Personal, 1968-01-09-1977-12-23
        - Autograph letters, 1968-01-09-1977-12-23; (2 folders) (Box 106)
        - Postcards and greeting cards, 1968 August 21 - 1970 August 11, undated (Box 106)
          Contains: 35 postcards (1968 August 21 - 1970 August 11); 41 greeting cards (undated).
      - Professional, 1968-10-1971-08
        - Professional correspondence, 1968-10-1971-08; (3 folders) (Box 107)
        - Professional correpondence, undated (Box 105)
    - Manuscripts, undated
      - "Prism Mirror Lens" (first chapter of 'Dhalgren'), fragments, undated; (6 folders) (Box 108)
        Contains: "Prism Mirror Lens" (first chapter of 'Dhalgren'), fragments. Also includes: portions of various short stories and "The Ruins of Morning" (section from 'Dhalgren').
      - 'Nova', undated; (2 folders) (Box 108)
      - Miscellaneous by SRD, undated
        - Short stories and non-fiction articles, undated (Box 108)
      - 'Commune and Communion', undated (Box 108)
        Contains: 'Commune and Communion', copies and fragments of non-ficton work.
      - Three scripts re: "Theresius", film by Robert Mooney (Box 108)
      - Fiction by various authors, undated (Box 108)
      - Thesis by David Ripper, "A Different Myth", undated (Box 108)
      - Poems by SRD and others, including Marilyn Hacker, undated; (2 folders) (Box 108)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 109)
        Contains: miscellaneous manuscripts.
    - Printed material (continued), 1967
      - 'Fire' (journal), 1967 (Box 109)
  - Materials deposited in April 2006, 2005-06-09; 1.08; (1 box)
    These materials were previously held on deposit at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center, Boston University. Samuel R. Delany deposited them in April 2006.
    - 'About Writing' proof, 2005-06-09 (Box 108)
      Contains: 'About Writing', page proof. Includes: holograph corrections by editor.
    - 'About Writing', draft, undated; (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - Materials deposited in May 2006, 1963-2009-11; 7.33; (8 boxes)
    These materials were previously held on deposit at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center, Boston University. Samuel R. Delany deposited them in May 2006.
    - Correspondence, 1965-2005
      - General correspondence, 2003; (8 folders) (Box 110)
      - General correspondence, 2004; (8 folders) (Box 110)
      - General correspondence, 2004; (5 folders) (Box 111)
      - General correspondence, 2005; (6 folders) (Box 111)
      - General correspondence, 1968-2002 (Box 111)
      - Frank mail, postcards, 1985-1988 (Box 111)
        Contains: frank mail; postcards. Includes: printed material; manuscripts; professional materials.
      - Correspondence with mother, Berry, Marilyn Hacker, 1965-1990 (Box 111)
        Contains: postcards, autograph letters, typed letters. Includes: memorabilia; manuscripts.
      - Correspondence with Alexei Panshin, 1977-1984, undated (Box 111)
        Contains: correspondence with Alexei Panshin, cards, autograph letters, typed letters (1977-1984, undated). Includes: photographs. Also includes: subfile titled "Searles & Last" (1976-1990).
      - Science Fiction World, 1975-1999, undated (Box 111)
        Contains: postcards, cards, email, typed letters. Includes: printed material; legal materials; manuscripts; memorabilia; professional materials.
    - Notebooks, 2002-12-2004-07
      - Notebooks, 2002-12-2004-07; (9 folders) (Box 112)
        Contains: nine notebooks, covering the date range of 2002 December - 2004 July.
    - Manuscripts, 1987-2004
      - By SRD, 1999-2004, undated; (3 folders) (Box 113)
      - Corrections, circa 2002; (2 folders) (Box 113)
      - By others, 1987-1993 (Box 113)
      - Prints of digital scans, undated (Box 132)
        Contains: printouts and photocopies of journal entries and writings, circa 1970s-1990s. Also includes: printouts and photocopies of correspondence and promotional materials.
    - Printed material, 1963-2005-08-18
      - Proofs, 1963-2005-08-18
        - 'About Writing', 2005-06-09-2005-08-18; (6 folders) (Box 113)
        - "Eden, Eden, Eden: Genesis ii, 4, to ii, 22", 2004-05-14 (Box 113)
        - 'The Fall of the Towers', 1963-2003, undated (Box 113)
        - 'Hogg', 2004, undated; (2 folders) (Box 113)
        - 'Hogg', 2004 (Box 114)
        - "Phallos", 2000-2004; (2 folders) (Box 114)
        - By others, 2003 (Box 114)
    - Professional materials, 2003-2005
      - Interviews, 2003-2004, undated; (3 folders) (Box 114)
        Contains: interviews. Also includes: correspondence.
      - Resume, class materials, 2003-2005 (Box 114)
        Contains: resume; class materials. Includes: printed materials; financial materials; legal materials.
    - Printed material (continued), 1995-2005
      - Booklets, pamphlets, and flyers, 2000-2005 (Box 115)
      - Articles, 1995-2005, undated; (2 folders) (Box 114)
      - Newspapers and newspaper clippings, 1996-2005, undated (Box 115)
      - Book covers, undated (Box 114)
      - Periodicals, 1996-2004 (Box 114)
    - Medical records, 2004-06-01
      - Lab reports, 2004-06-01 (Box 114)
    - Financial materials, 1994-2005
      - Statements, tax forms, receipts, 1994-2005 (Box 114)
        Contains: statements (1994-2005); tax forms (2000-2004); receipts (2000-2001). Includes: correspondence.
    - Legal materials, 2003-03-28
      - Contract, 2003-03-28 (Box 114)
    - Personal memorabilia, 2002-04-2009-11
      - Quotes printed onto sticker labels, undated (Box 114)
      - Ticket, plastic "Happy New Year" necklace, hospital wristband, Paul Robeson stamps, 2002-2009, undated (Box 114)
        Contains: ticket (2009 November 6); plastic "Happy New Year" necklace (undated); hospital wristband (2002 April 3); Paul Robeson stamps (undated).
    - Photographs, 2002-2004-04
      - Photoprints of Leon Forest Lecture at Northwestern University and outings with friends, 2004-01-2004-04 (Box 114)
        Contains: 34 color photoprints. Also includes: correspondence.
      - Recording of SRD on "The Paula Gordon Show", 2002; 1 (Box 245)
  - Materials deposited in 2009, 1948-2012; 20.58; (20 boxes)
    These materials were previously held on deposit at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center, Boston University. Samuel R. Delany deposited them in 2009.
    - Manuscripts, 1960-2009
      - Files (may include typescript drafts by SRD, holograph notes, correspondence), 1989-07-1990-06
        - "The Bantam 16th Printing Line Corrections", undated (Box 116)
        - "David Samuelson July '89 - June '90", 1989-07-1990-06 (Box 116)
          Includes: typed letter from SRD to David Samuelson re: SRD's comments/refelections on 'Nova'.
        - Untitled regarding various draft fragments by SRD, undated (Box 116)
          Includes: typed letter by SRD.
        - Untitled regarding 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders'; Untitled regarding 'Nova', undated (Box 116)
          Contains: Untitled regarding 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', including correspondence; Untitled regarding 'Nova', including corrections to various works, artwork.
      - By SRD, 1994-2009
        - Novels, undated; (16 folders) (Box 116)
          Contains: 'About Writing: Seven Essays, Four Letters and Five Interviews', 2 typescipt drafts and draft fragments (folders 4-6); 'Dark Reflections', typescript drafts, chapter fragments (folders 7-19).
        - Novels, 1994-2005, undated; (17 folders) (Box 117)
          Contains: 'Dark Reflections', drafts, chapter fragments, undated (folders 1-4); 'The Grand Masque', draft, undated (folder 5); 'The Mad Man', draft, 1994 March 5 (folder 6); 'Phallos', 6 drafts, articles, reviews, fragments, undated (folders 7-11); 'Shoat Rumblin', draft, draft fragments, outlines, proposals, 2005 April (folders 12-13); 'This Short Day of Frost and Sun', draft, undated (folder 14); 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', drafts, draft fragments, undated (folders 15-17).
        - Novels, undated; (5 folders) (Box 118)
          Contains: 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', drafts, draft fragments, undated.
        - Novels, undated; (12 folders) (Box 119)
          Contains: 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', drafts, draft fragments, undated (folders 1-11); 'Valley of Ashes', 2 drafts, chapter fragments, undated (folder 12).
        - Short stories, 2009, undated; (2 folders) (Box 119)
          Contains: "Aye, and Gomorrah...", draft, correspondence, 2009 January 25 (folder 13); "The Depraved", draft, fragment, undated (folder 14); "The Owls, or Death and the Labyrinth", 3 drafts, outline, articles, undated (folder 14); "The Prize", 3 drafts, 1 draft fragment, undated (folder 14).
        - Academic non-fiction, undated; (2 folders) (Box 119)
          Contains: "Atlantis: Model 24 (A Commentary on Hart Crane's The Bridge)", draft (folder 15); "Generic Views: 'Starboard Wine' and other essays: Notes on the Language of Science Fiction", draft (folder 15); "The Discourse of Desire - Broken Copy", incomplete draft (folder 16).
        - Essays, 1998-2006; (2 folders) (Box 120)
          Contains: "Another Time, Another Place..." (undated); "Epic & Everyday", draft (2005 January); "The Gamble", 3 drafts (2004 August 1); "Historifying Marginal Practices" (undated); "In the Once Upon a Time City", 2 drafts (undated); "Notes on 'The Star-Pit'", 3 (?) drafts (1998 November); "Samuel R. Delany, Age 54", draft (undated); "Starboard Wine and Other Essays: Notes on the Language of Science Fiction" (undated); untitled re: request to revew Tom Disch, draft (2006 December 13).
        - Articles, 2000-2007, undated (Box 120)
          Contains: "Critical THeory and Science Fiction: A Writer's Preface", includes holograph notes (2000 August); "Eleusis: Of Friedrich Holderlin", 2 drafts (2003 November 26); "The Life of/and Writing" (undated); "Looking Back at the Autumnal City", draft (2001); "Now, Come Fire...: Friedrich Holderlin", draft (2003 November 26); "On Calvino's Memos", draft (2007 April); "The Politics of Disaster: Fiction, Poetry, and Sex in Joanna Russ's 'Souls'", draft (2002 December 21); "Variables in Gay Slang/Constants in Gay Oppression", draft, includes articles and magazines (undated).
        - Book reviews, 2001-2005, undated (Box 120)
          Contains: "Anabasis: Joseph Conrad, Willa Cather, & Peter Jackson" (undated); "A Centennial Life from the Roaring Twenties", 2 drafts (2001 October); "The Man Who Lost the Sea: Volume X: The Complete Stories of Theodore Sturgeon", draft (2005 May 25); "A Note on Bruce Nugent's 'Smoke, Lilies and Jade'", draft (undated); "A Personal Note on Ashbery", draft (2004 September 7).
        - Speeches, 2006-2009, undated (Box 120)
          Contains: "Acceptance Speech", draft (2008 April 29); "Art and Aids" (2006 December 1); "Farewell Comment for Alan Singer to Read Out at the Temple Student Graduation Reading, Wherever He Thinks Fit", draft (undated); "Introduction for Dylan Perrota and Neil Gaiman" (undated); "Introduction for Junot Diaz, the Lannan Foundation", draft (2009 January 21); "Introduction for Peter Carey" (2007 April); "Once you go black" (undated); "Pilgrim Award Acceptance Speech" (undated).
      - "Speech" by Iva Hacker-Delany, undated (Box 120)
        Contains: "Speech" by Iva Hacker-Delany, typescript.
      - "Le Bateau Ivre", poem by Arthur Rimbaud (translated "The Drunken Ship" by SRD), 1960 (Box 120)
        Contains: "Le Bateau Ivre", poem by Arthur Rimbaud (translated "The Drunken Ship" by SRD), typescript.
      - Interviews featuring SRD, 1995-2009
        - "Adam Roberts interviews Samuel R. Delany", re: values and cultures, 2003-07-09 (Box 120)
          Contains: typescript, 2 copies.
        - "A Conversation between Darieck Scott and Samuel R. Delany", undated (Box 120)
        - "A Conversation with Samuel Delany" by Carl Freedman, undated (Box 120)
          Contains: "A Conversation with Samuel Delany" by Carl Freedman, 3 typescript drafts re: 'Dark Reflections'.
        - "A Conversation with Samuel R. Delany" by Jayme Blaschke, 2001-04 (Box 120)
          Contains: "A Conversation with Samuel R. Delany" by Jayme Blaschke, typescript with holograph notes re: re-issues and career.
        - "The Cusack Interview" by Erin Cusack, 2005-05-14 (Box 120)
          Contains: "The Cusack Interview" by Erin Cusack, typescript, regarding the Comics Art Form.
        - "Herukhuti Interviews Samuel Delany" by Herukuti, 2003-06-03-2003-07-03 (Box 120)
          Contains: "Herukhuti Interviews Samuel Delany" by Herukuti, typescript, 4 copies, re: personal life.
        - "An Interview with Samuel R. Delany" by Jayme Lynn Blaschke, 2001-04 (Box 120)
          Contains: "An Interview with Samuel R. Delany" by Jayme Lynn Blaschke, typescript with holograph notes, regarding SRD career. Includes: printed materials.